calculator.net 2018-06-07

# About Us

We are a group of IT professionals enthusiastic in creating quality free tools and content on the internet. The main purpose of this website is to provide a comprehensive collection of free online calculators for the ease of public use. This site was launched on calculators.info first in 2007. In 2008, we purchased and migrated to calculator.net.

More than 99% of the calculators on this site were developed in-house. Some calculators use open-source JavaScript components under different open-source licenses. More than 80% of the calculators are based on well-known formulas or equations from textbooks, such as the mortgage calculator, BMI calculator, etc. If formulas are controversial, we provide the results of all popular formulas, as can be seen in the Ideal Weight Calculator. Calculators such as the love calculator that are solely meant for amusement are based on internal formulas. The results of the financial calculators were reviewed by our financial advisors, who work for major personal financial advising firms. The results of the health calculators were reviewed and approved by local medical doctors. More than 95% of the descriptive content was developed in-house with a small amount of content taken from wikipedia.org under the GNU Free Documentation License. The descriptive content of the financial calculators was created and reviewed by our financial team. The descriptive content of the health calculators was reviewed by local medical doctors. The rest of the descriptive content was created by our own team. In addition to this site, we also have free apps for mobile visitors.

This site is owned and operated by Maple Tech. International LLC.

### Contact Us

We can be reached via the following form. Normally, we will respond within 2 business days.

### Mailing Address:

2203 Timberloch Pl  
Suite 252  
The Woodlands, TX 77380

|   
---|---  
  
### Copyright

The logos, images, scripts, and individual pages are copyrighted material. The materials on this site cannot be copied/modified without permission.

### Privacy Policy

Maple Tech International LLC operates the calculator.net website, which provides the SERVICE.

This page is used to inform website visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service.

If you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation with this policy. The Personal Information that we collect are used for providing and improving the Service. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Information Collection and Use**

We take and respect your privacy seriously. We may collect information via cookie or web log. This is to customize services and enhance customer satisfaction.

The data we collect are:

**Log Data**

We want to inform you that whenever you visit our Service, we collect information that your browser sends to us that is called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser version, pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, and other statistics.

**Cookies and Third Party Advertising**

Cookies are files with small amount of data that is commonly used an anonymous unique identifier. These are sent to your browser from the website that you visit and are stored on your computer's hard drive.

Our website uses these "cookies" to collection information and to improve our Service. You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies, and know when a cookie is being sent to your computer. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

**Web Forms on Our Site**

The information you fill and submit by the web forms on our sites, to enable the unit converters to function.

**Security**

We value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Links to Other Sites**

Our Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by us. Therefore, we strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.

**Children's Privacy**

Our Services do not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under 13. In the case we discover that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us so that we will be able to do necessary actions.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

We reserves the right to update this privacy policy with or without notice. Thus, we advise you to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately, after they are posted on this page.

### Terms of Use

By using our services, you agree to be bound by the following terms and conditions (the "Terms of Use").

We have no control over any potential changes to content that we link to. As such, we provide no guarantees and take no responsibility regarding changes to, or the accuracy of content that we link to, as it is possible that changes that do not align with our original intent could be made after our initial link to the site. If any inaccuracies or broken links are found, feel free to contact us using the form above, and any issues will be addressed as necessary.

THE MATERIALS ON THIS SITE ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" AND WITHOUT WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED.

We reserve the right to update the Privacy Policy and Terms of Use with or without notice.
